(Sheldon:)Good morning, Amy.
(Amy:)It most assuredly is not.
(Sheldon:)Are you experiencing
dehydration, headache,
(Sheldon:)nausea and shame?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Amy:)I also found a Korean man's
business card
(Amy:)tucked into my cleavage.
(Amy:)What happened last night?
Ah, memory impairment;
(Sheldon:)the free prize at the bottom
of every vodka bottle.
(Amy:)Sheldon?
(Priya:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Last night you gave me
some excellent advice
(Sheldon:)regarding my problem here
at home,
(Sheldon:)you kissed me and then vomited
on and off for 40 minutes,
(Sheldon:)following which you passed out
on your bathroom floor.
(Sheldon:)I then folded a towel under
your head as a pillow,
(Sheldon:)set your oven clock
to the correct time
(Sheldon:)because it was
driving me crazy...
(Sheldon:)...and I left.
(Penny:)Okay.
(Amy:)Don't really know
where we go from here.
(Sheldon:)I suggest
we treat our relationship
(Sheldon:)as if it were
a crashed computer
(Sheldon:)and restore it to the last point
we both agree it worked.
(Amy:)Terrific. Thank you.
(Amy:)They were out of menthols!
(Amy:)Get off my back!
(Amy:)Not easy living with a
temperamental little primate.
(Leonard(off):)Come on, Priya,
just admit I embarrass you!
(Sheldon:)You're preaching
to the choir, sister.